http://www.cording.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Your PrivacyI believe your privacy to be important. To better protect your privacy I provide this notice explaining my online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, I make it available on my homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
Product DeliveryMy digital products are delivered via a link sent by email. On rare occasions an email can be delayed or missed, or end up in a junk folder. If you don’t receive an email containing the download link within a few hours after placing an order, please contact me and I will send you a fresh download link.
Refund / Exchange and Limitation of LiabilitySince I offer non-tangible, irrevocable, digital goods, I do not issue refunds based on satisfaction. All sales are final and I do not offer exchanges on my music. You are responsible for understanding my refund policy before making a purchase.
In no event will I be held liable for:
(i) any incidental, consequential, or indirect damages (including, but not limited to damages for loss of profits, business interruption, expenses, other damages or costs, attorney’s fees, or any other negative impacts) arising out of the use of or inability to use my music, or download of my music, or any delay in receiving my music, or
(ii) any claim attributable to errors, omissions, or other inaccuracies in my music and/or musical materials downloaded or delivered from this site.
All the music found here is protected by international copyright. You may not modify, copy, reproduce, republish, upload, post, transmit, or distribute, in any manner, the music from this site. You may download and print music you have purchased from this site for your own use.
Collection of Personal InformationWhen visiting Cording.org, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Any personally identifiable information you may choose to provide, in order to obtain newsletters, services or products, is never shared with any third parties except as may be required by law to comply with issues of national security or law enforcement. I do not sell your personal information to anyone for any purpose. Period.
I make every reasonable effort to safeguard your personal information, but please recognize that no procedure or method employed to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure is ever 100% secure.
Also be aware that you are responsible for the personal information you share in publicly viewable areas, such as comment posts, etc., and that information may become public immediately. Please take care when using these features.
Links to third party WebsitesI have included links on this site for your use and reference. I am not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from my own.
Changes to this Privacy StatementThe contents of these statements may be altered at any time, at my discretion.
If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of Cording.org you may contact me by using the email link appearing at the bottom of every page.
Last updated Fri, 12 Sep 2014 11:28
Search
Search for:
This Day In HistoryBorn This Day1803 Hector Berlioz was born in 18031908 Elliott Carter was born in 1908Upcoming events:
Sat23Jan2021
Fernwood String Quartet7 PM or 9 PMDr. Phillips Center for Performing Arts, Alexis & Jim Pugh Theater, 445 S Magnolia Av, Orlando FL 32801Program by Fernwood String Quartet of world-premieres by Central Florida composers.
Follow this link for ticket purchase.
Social distancing of 6+ feet throughout building. Reduced capacity seating (30%)
Contactless temperature check at entry. Touchless hand sanitizer stations.
Face coverings required at all times (except when actively eating or drinking).
Cashless transactions encouraged.
Performers:
Program:
Tickets start at $35, single tickets or tables of 4 available.
Table or seating assignments sent within a week of order.
Archives
October 2020 (1)
May 2020 (1)
October 2019 (1)
September 2019 (1)
February 2018 (1)
February 2017 (1)
January 2016 (1)
March 2015 (1)
December 2014 (1)
September 2014 (1)
August 2014 (1)
January 2014 (2)
December 2013 (13)
November 2013 (4)
December 2012 (6)
July 2012 (1)
February 2012 (2)
September 2011 (1)
August 2011 (1)
May 2011 (2)
March 2011 (3)
July 2009 (1)
May 2009 (4)
April 2009 (1)
February 2008 (3)
January 2008 (1)
October 2007 (1)
August 2007 (1)
June 2007 (2)
April 2007 (1)
January 2007 (2)
December 2006 (4)
October 2006 (1)
June 2006 (1)
December 2005 (1)
November 2005 (1)
September 2005 (3)
July 2005 (4)
March 2005 (1)
February 2005 (1)
January 2005 (1)
December 2004 (1)
September 2004 (1)
Copyright © 2004-2020 Cording.org
